'Bi.
What?
There's something I need you to do.
Ms. Talia?
- Yes?
- Ms. Talia, hi.
Do you remember me?
- I know that the reason--
- [ENGINE ROARING]
- Hey! Hey!
- [TALIA GASPS]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE ROARING]
[TALIA] Oh! Oh my God!
[GASPS] Are you okay?
Oh my goodness!
- Oh…
- [BEA GRUNTS]
You're wounded!
[SOFT GROAN] I'm okay, ma'am.
- Are you okay?
- Yes. Here's your bag.
- Hi!
- [HR OFFICER] Hi.
You didn't call me.
Never mind, that's okay.
[CALOY] Sorry.
I was too rough, so you got dragged.
It's fine. It made our act
even more convincing.
Ms. Talia really felt bad for me.
- [MARJ] I think it's perfect.
- Guys?
So, I have good news.
I have a potential sponsor,
and it's…
Talia & Co., the jewelry brand!
[GIGGLES]
Wow!
They just have one request, though.
Okay…
[TALIA] So we are continuing this campaign
with our next partner,
Billy Cariño of LoveList.
She is the perfect next partner for us.
They want you to wear this
to the awards night.
This necklace costs 30 million.
[BILLY] Wow.
[CHARM] It's beautiful!
[TALIA] What do you think?
It's a great idea, right?
What do you think?
- What do you think?
- Sounds great!
Yes!
Uh, Bea?
- Ma'am?
- [TALIA] Yes?
Yes, I agree with you, Ms. Talia!
Very good.
I think she'll make a wonderful partner
for our event.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[JORDAN SIGHS]
Dude, I'm sorry.
I searched every corner of the Net.
Mm-hmm.
But I couldn't find anything
about Bea's father
or her family.
Well,
It's hard to find someone
who doesn't want to be found.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe they have prior criminal records.
But I'm sorry, dude…
I know you don't--
That's enough apologies.
- Stop it.
- What?
Come on, stop it!
Thank you for taking the time
to look for Bea's father.
And don't worry.
I already have a plan for Bea and Caloy.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Now go away.
[BILLY GIGGLES]
We hit the jackpot with this!
But more importantly,
this will be a huge blow to Billy!
Okay.
Just tell me when and where.
I'll do anything for you.
It's for us.
I'll hang up now.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
IF YOU EVER NEED HELP, I'M HERE.
- Look at that beautiful smile!
- [PRECIOUS CHUCKLES]
I just saw a funny meme.
- Really?
- Yes.
Okay. A meme from Brandon?
What? No. You're so silly!
- You know what, Auntie Pres?
- What?
Happiness looks good on you.
I hope you always stay happy.
Mm-hmm. I hope you do too.
I hope you stay happy
despite all the challenges you're facing.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I can handle it.
Especially since I have people
around me who help me.
- Come with me. Let's go.
- Brandon, that hurts!
Bro.
Don't force her to come
if she doesn't want to.
You should go.
I'll call security if you don't.
Brandon, please just leave.
- I can fight you, you know?
- Hey! Oliver!
Break it up!
Go back to your classroom.
What are you all looking at?
Go back to your classrooms.
- That's right.
- Mm.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- ♪ Baby, I… ♪
- [GUITAR STRUMMING]
[HUMMING]
[JORDAN] Sorry. I'll do it again. Ready?
♪ You matter more to me than being right ♪
♪ Baby, I won't be long ♪
♪ I'll be back by the end of the song ♪
What do you think?
It's okay, boss,
but it lacks emotion.
It's missing that emotional punch.
I agree, boss. How about this?
Just imagine you're singing
to the love of your life.
That's it.
You know, Robbie is right.
Do it this way.
Pretend you still love me.
Go on. One more time.
No, it's good enough.
Jordan…
The organizer of the PBS Executive
Circle Awards is a friend of mine.
I recommended you because I know you.
When you sing, you give us all the feels.
But why do you seem so distracted today?
Because of Billy.
What?
I mean, because you're dealing
with Billy's problems.
Because it also affects LoveList.
I know that.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Go. One more time.
- Go! Yes!
- Let's go.
- [ROBBIE] Let's go!
- [VALERIE] Whoo!
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
♪ Can we take a rest? ♪
So? How does it look?
[CHARM] Wow, it's so pretty!
- It's so pretty, right?
- Definitely worth 30 million!
Keep your eyes on it later, okay?
We can't afford to lose it.
Diamond represents power, so you go, girl!
- [CHARM] It's so pretty and shiny.
- Yeah, it looks good on you.
But, you know,
I feel like it would look better on me.
Because I have a longer neck
and I'm paler than you.
[CHUCKLING AWKWARDLY]
- You're so funny.
- You know what?
You should try tourmaline
to attract good vibes.
I agree.
- Yours is pretty, too.
- [MARJ] You already have one.
So funny. It looks good.
You know, guys,
I think we should get some coffee.
The event isn't until later. Come on.
- [MARJ] Right.
- [CHARM] Oh, perfect.
Ralph is downstairs.
Let's ask him to treat us.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Wait, wait.
What about the necklace?
[VALERIE] I'll…
I got it.
- [MARJ] Okay.
- Hold on.
- Keep it safe.
- Don't lose it.
Yes.
- Billy, be careful with it.
- Go. Keep it safe.
- [BILLY] Yes!
- It's expensive.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[CARS HONKING IN DISTANCE]
I hope our luck continues.
Our numbers are doing good,
thanks to Happily Ever After!
It's not just luck, Toni.
We worked hard for all of this.
My investment in LoveList was worth it.
- So, cheers to that.
- [TONI] Yes!
[CHARM] Well, hopefully,
your mom feels the same way.
So she can be assured that
your money didn't go to waste.
Why? It's your money anyway, Ralph, right?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Um…
Well, in their family,
one person's money is everyone's money.
They're a big corporation, so technically,
the money invested in us
is the family's company money.
Is that a bad thing?
Definitely bad.
I mean, if you actually
want to get married
and lead your own home one day.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
See?
Look at how obvious it is, babe.
Even at this point, you can't make
decisions completely on your own.
It's as if your umbilical cord
is still tied to your family,
especially to your mother.
Well, maybe they're just
looking out for me.
[CHARM] Looking out for you? Why?
Am I a danger to you, huh?
[SCOFFS] Here we go again.
- [GLASS CLINKS]
- Ralph, Charm.
We keep going in circles.
- [RALPH SCOFFS]
- [CHAIR SCRAPING]
Guys, excuse me.
[CHARM] Ralph!
- [RALPH SCOFFS]
- Ralph!
[RALPH] Sorry, bro.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh my.
Their lover's quarrel came
at the wrong time.
I know, right?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
Water, water. Hmmm…
Two towels.
And two tissues.
Okay, this will be fine.
Hey, handsome.
Yes, sir?
I saw you earlier.
What about it?
Would you like to be famous?
But, sir, I might get…
Here, call me later. Take my number.
Here, when you get home.
But, sir, I might get fired for that.
I'll just slide it into your pocket.
Oh, okay, okay, sir.
- I might get fired, sir.
- Open it later.
[CHUCKLES] You're quite the macho guy.
- Okay. Thank you, sir.
- Call me, okay?
[HOUSEKEEPER] Housekeeping!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello.
Okay.
Thank you.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE THUDDING]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT THUDDING]
[SOFT THUD]
[DOOR CREAKING OPEN]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[JORDAN, CALOY GRUNTING]
- Dude!
- Get off me!
- [PEPPER SPRAY HISSES]
- [SCREAMS]
[BILLY] Jordan! The necklace!
- Go, go, go!
- [BILLY] Run!
- [CALOY] Get back here!
- Go!
I'll kill both of you!
- [BILLY] Jordan, let's go!
- Give me the necklace!
- [CALOY GRUNTS]
- [JORDAN] Stay back. Stay back.
[CALOY BREATHING HEAVILY]
Give me back the necklace,
or I'll kill you.
- Put the knife down.
- Give it to me!
- I'll give it to you. Just don't--
- I'll kill you if you don't.
- Jordan!
- It's yours, it's yours.
Give it to me!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
- Hands in the air!
[OFFICER 1] Hands in the air!
No sudden movements!
[OFFICER] Cuff him!
Don't make any sudden movements.
- [OFFICER 2] Let the knife go!
- [CALOY] Fine!
- [CALOY] There!
- Let it go!
[CALOY GRUNTING IN PAIN]
[CALOY BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [CALOY] I'll come back for you.
- [OFFICER] Don't do anything stupid.
[CHUCKLING] You set me up?
You set me up, huh?!
- [CALOY BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [OFFICER 1] Get out!
- Just wait until I get out.
- [OFFICERS GRUNT]
You didn't fight fair!
[OFFICER 2] Let's go! Come on!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Move!
Go! Move!
Stop resisting!
[GRUNTS] Move!
- Get inside! Go!
- [CALOY] Wait.
- Stop resisting!
- [CALOY] Hold on.
- Get in!
- [CALOY GRUNTS] Sir…
- [SIGHS]
- [OFFICER] Let's go!
Justice said "not today"
and karma handled it.
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
Okay, that's it for today's meeting.
I'll see you again next week.
Ma'am, I'll take care of this.
See you! Take care!
Ms. Beatrice Mercado?
You need to come with us
to the police station now.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, your plan worked.
Because of you, Ms. Talia.
I am not considering
Bea Mercado for the position,
especially with her track record.
- Mm-hm.
- But…
when I found out that her
case is involved with you,
I called you.
I'm worried about you, Billy.
Thank you, Ms. Talia.
She says the accusations
against her are not true.
- Mm.
- So…
I wanted to get your side of the story.
There's only one thing
you need to know, Ms. Talia.
You can't trust Bea Mercado.
And I can prove that.
How?
I'll be needing your help.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Ever since we rolled out this campaign,
there has been an increase in
the number of our followers.
And of course, this translates into
sales!
So we are continuing this campaign
with our next partner,
Billy Cariño of LoveList.
She is the perfect next partner for us.
More than just having a big following
and being a businesswoman,
she is relevant.
[BEA] We hit the jackpot with this!
But more importantly,
this will be a huge blow to Billy!
Good thing she took the bait.
Thank you.
Billy, anything for you.
In fact, I should be the one to thank you.
You know that I almost gave up on love.
I thought it was too late
for me to find someone.
If not for LoveList and you,
maybe I would not have found my forever.
So…
thank you very much.
I have to go.
[HOPEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Happy anniversary, my love.
[GASPS] They're beautiful.
Of course.
Thank you.
Okay.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEA] I don't care
about that Billy.
And most importantly,
I don't care about you.
'Bi, don't say that.
[BEA] Don't touch me!
I never asked him to do anything
because I don't even know him!
[MARIELA] When will you leave
my daughter alone?
Like I told you before,
it's your daughter
you need to talk to.
And we'll let the world know
that she's also a criminal.
Can you please talk
to your people?
Maybe they want to know
what a real criminal is.
Do you think
you're going to scare me?
Enjoy your freedom,
because it won't last long.
It's way past your 10-day deadline
with Boss Zandro.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
[NURSE] You're listed as
an emergency contact.
For patient Enrico Dominguez.
- That's your problem!
- Jordan!
My friend has nothing
to do with it, okay?!
All he's missing is a girlfriend.
We'll find one for him.
♪ Baby, I won't be long ♪
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]